<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<reuters>
<newsitem itemid="2330" id="root" date="1996-08-20" xml:lang="en">
<title>USA: Tylan stock jumps; weighs sale of company.</title>
<headline>Tylan stock jumps; weighs sale of company.</headline>
<dateline>SAN DIEGO</dateline>
<text>
<p>The stock of Tylan General Inc. jumped Tuesday after the maker of
process-management equipment said it is exploring the sale of the
company and added that it has already received some inquiries from
potential buyers.</p>
<p>Tylan was up $2.50 to $12.75 in early trading on the Nasdaq market.</p>
<p>The company said it has set up a committee of directors to oversee
the sale and that Goldman, Sachs &amp; Co. has been retained as its
financial adviser.</p>
</text>
<copyright>(c) Reuters Limited 1996</copyright>
<metadata>
<codes class="bip:countries:1.0">
<code code="USA"> </code>
</codes>
<codes class="bip:industries:1.0">
<code code="I34420"> </code>
</codes>
<codes class="bip:topics:1.0">
<code code="C15"> </code>
<code code="C152"> </code>
<code code="C18"> </code>
<code code="C181"> </code>
<code code="CCAT"> </code>
</codes>
<dc element="dc.publisher" value="Reuters Holdings Plc"/>
<dc element="dc.date.published" value="1996-08-20"/>
<dc element="dc.source" value="Reuters"/>
<dc element="dc.creator.location" value="SAN DIEGO"/>
<dc element="dc.creator.location.country.name" value="USA"/>
<dc element="dc.source" value="Reuters"/>
</metadata>
</newsitem>
<newsitem itemid="2286" id="root" date="1996-08-20" xml:lang="en">
<title>MEXICO: Recovery excitement brings Mexican markets to life.</title>
<headline>Recovery excitement brings Mexican markets to life.</headline>
<byline>Henry Tricks</byline>
<dateline>MEXICO CITY</dateline>
<text>
<p>Emerging evidence that Mexico's economy was back on the recovery track sent Mexican markets into
a buzz of excitement Tuesday, with stocks closing at record highs and interest rates at 19-month lows.</p>
<p>"Mexico has been trying to stage a recovery since the beginning of this year and it's always been
getting ahead of itself in terms of fundamentals," said Matthew Hickman of Lehman Brothers in New York.</p>
<p>"Now we're at the point where the fundamentals are with us. The history is now falling out of
view."</p>
<p>That history is one etched into the minds of all investors in Mexico: an economy in crisis since
December 1994, a free-falling peso and stubbornly high interest rates.</p>
<p>This week, however, second-quarter gross domestic product was reported up 7.2 percent, much
stronger than most analysts had expected. Interest rates on governent Treasury bills, or Cetes, in the
secondary market fell on Tuesday to 23.90 percent, their lowest level since Jan. 25, 1995.</p>
<p>The stock market's main price index rallied 77.12 points, or 2.32 percent, to a record 3,401.79 points,
with volume at a frenzied 159.89 million shares.</p>
<p>Confounding all expectations has been the strength of the peso, which ended higher in its longer-term
contracts on Tuesday despite the secondary Cetes drop and expectations of lower benchmark rates in
Tuesday's weekly auction.</p>
<p>With U.S. long-term interest rates expected to remain steady after the Federal Reserve refrained from
raising short-term rates on Tuesday, the attraction of Mexico, analysts say, is that it offers robust returns for
foreigners and growing confidence that they will not fall victim to a crumbling peso.</p>
<p>"The focus is back on Mexican fundamentals," said Lars Schonander, head of researcher at
Santander in Mexico City. "You have a continuing decline in inflation, a stronger-than-expected GDP growth
figure and the lack of any upward move in U.S. rates."</p>
<p>Other factors were also at play, said Felix Boni, head of research at James Capel in Mexico City,
such as positive technicals and economic uncertainty in Argentina, which has put it and neighbouring Brazil's
markets at risk.</p>
<p>"There's a movement out of South American markets into Mexico," he said. But Boni was also wary of
what he said could be "a lot of hype."</p>
<p>The economic recovery was still export-led, and evidence was patchy that the domestic consumer
was back with a vengeance. Also, corporate earnings need to grow strongly to justify the run-up in the stock
market, he said.</p>
</text>
<copyright>(c) Reuters Limited 1996</copyright>
<metadata>
<codes class="bip:countries:1.0">
<code code="MEX"> </code>
</codes>
<codes class="bip:topics:1.0">
<code code="E11"> </code>
<code code="ECAT"> </code>
<code code="M11"> </code>
<code code="M12"> </code>
<code code="MCAT"> </code>
</codes>
<dc element="dc.publisher" value="Reuters Holdings Plc" />
<dc element="dc.date.published" value="1996-08-20" />
<dc element="dc.source" value="Reuters" />
<dc element="dc.creator.location" value="MEXICO CITY" />
<dc element="dc.creator.location.country.name" value="MEXICO" />
<dc element="dc.source" value="Reuters" />
</metadata>
</newsitem>
</reuters>
